This Subtitle Downloaded From Subtitlez.com
Okay girls, come on.
Chin up, shoulders back.
Hi. What brings you here?
Sodhi ji texted me about a boy.
Don't make faces.
Don't make that face.
The boy can meet us on only one day.
On the day of the pageant.
Sodhiji says we must mark that day as
"free" in the diary.
Mom, you told your boyfriend...
You told your boyfriend
to find a match for me.
What choice do I have?
You are a grownup now.
And I am a single mom.
Not again.
You are a recovering thalassemic.
Don't expect a long queue
of grooms waiting for you.
We will have to hustle.
No hustles, please.
- Then what else?
- Fall in love.
Once-in-a-lifetime love.
For that, you need
to have 200 affairs first.
We don't have that much time.
You are just in a hurry
to marry your boyfriend Sodhiji.
First, you were waiting for me to die.
And now you are eager
to get me married.
You think I am one of those mothers.
Am I?
Like way, mother.
Come on, slap me.
Beat me, Beat me.
Happy, mom, what are you doing?
Are you okay?
- Hit me.
- Stop this nonsense.
Let's go.
Am I one of those mothers?
Go ahead and invite him.
Invite him to the pageant.
The groom?
To the Ms. May Queen Pageant?
Are you out of your mind?
This is reality, mom.
I wanted to be Ms. May Queen.
Since I was this ye tall,
that's how long.
Earlier, I couldn't participate
because of my condition.
But now I am disease-free.
So why should anything stop me?
Tell me.
Is it right to stop me?
Is it right?
Nothing will stop you.
One minute.
Hello. Sodhiji.
We need to discuss something.
Move. Out of my way.
Let me and my wife get off.
Please. Please.
Ladies coming through.
Hey What are you upto?
why are you standing in middle,
get side.
Come, dear.
The 7:30 Local.
Here a man is not a man
but like chicken.
Sorry
Excuse me.
Side, please.
Hanging on like the rest of the herd.
to become the lunch of Mumbai.
You have a new voice message.
Hello. 30th June.
It's my wedding.
If you don't show up,
I will make your life miserable.
Wedding?
Point a finger towards it.
Yes, nice. Very nice.
One second.
Okay Ma'am... Sure ma'am...
Bajju.
Hello. Laadli.
I am shocked.
Where are you?
Am I looking alright...
Currently, I am shooting
my pre-wedding video.
But is he your trophy or aunt's?
Mom, obviously.
Yes, they actually met here.
It was an unusual meeting.
"Alls well that ends in wedding bells."
She's the one who used
to go out fishing every day.
Non-stop.
So, Shimla,
the moment has arrived when we find out.
Who will be Ms. May Queen Shimla, 2023?
So, ladies and gentlemen--
Boys and girls.
She is a single mother,
but family is very good...
Come on Abhay be quick.
- Selecting beautiful girls who represents...
- We are already late.
Our beautiful hill town internationally.
Thanks.
If you wouldn't have kept
so much busy to yourself.
Then would have met girl at home.
And Miss universe...
And our first runner-up is...
- ...the fair and lovely...Ms. Tarana Dhanda.
- Hi.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
I am so sorry I am late.
It's fine.
And finally, our
Ms. May shining Queen is...
- The shining beauty
- Isn't she Laadli.
Ms. Laadli Chibber.
"Don't stare with your wicked eyes."
"I'll fall in love."
"Don't tease me
with your killer attitude."
"I'll lose my heart."
Wow keep clapping... don't stop.
Congratulations to Ladli Chibber...
So Ladli what would you like to say.
So, what would you like to say?
Sorry, people.
But I can't stand corruption.
Your May Queen Laadli Chibbar.
Her mother is having an affair.
Affair.
With the biggest sponsor
of this beauty contest,
Sodhi and Son's MD.
Hence, the crown.
Actually,
the crown rightfully belongs to...
Tarana Dhanda.
- Congratulations, Tarana.
- Thank you.
Let's have a big round of applause...
come on guys applaud.
Long live Divorce Wife's Club.
Long live marriage.
- Sir...
- Long live Divorce Wife's Club.
- Long live marriage.
-Hurry up.
- Long live Divorce Wife's Club.
-Excuse me. Switch off the sound.
Hello. Yes?
Yes.
Okay, just one second.
Child...
they are waiting for you.
Mom, you are joking.
They are good people.
Let's be a little good.
My good girl.
They are waiting.
Sit.
I am Abhay.
I am Laadli.
Please be nice. Love you.
Samosa (Fritter).
It's from the pre-beauty contest.
It's baked.
No, thank you.
Something cold, then.
Zero calories.
No, it's okay.
A RayBan?
What?
Sunglasses for protection.
Too much shiny, you see.
Mom told me to put on something sober
before meeting you.
But I didn't have the time to change.
"My beloved"
No, no, it's absolutely fine.
Were you told about my medical history
and then invited here?
Or were you given
the sanitised version?
What?
Give me your number.
These are my medical reports.
I am a recovering thalassemic patient.
I know.
That's good then.
In the face of so much honesty,
even I have a confession to make.
I was in a long-term relationship.
And I didn't want to meet you
because I thought I was still not over her.
- But mom's--
- Pressure?
I've an old tryst
with this kind of pressure.
In fact,
we have a special name for it.
Repaying the nappy changer's debt.
"Your wicked eyes"
I think I'll have your zero-calorie Coke.
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
"Your wicked eyes"
Oh my god.
Aunty finally got Laadli hitched.
I can't believe it.
Whether with tears in your eyes,
a smile on your face,
or through plain struggle.
But you have to repay...
the nappy changer's debt.
In our family, this is life.
You're sitting next to the boss,
and still, you're late.
Brave man you are...
Mr. Bajrang Das Khatri.
Very brave. Very brave.
Sorry, sir.
Far away from my home,
getting choked in this office all day,
I am repaying this debt too.
And by choosing arranged
marriage over love,
so is Laadli.
But those who don't have to repay
this debt are called...
Lucky.
Shikhar!
Simran, I am slowing down.
Talk to him.
Shikhar, you are dead.
I am going to kill you.
Why?
I am not running with him,
I am running from you.
Just shut up, Simran.
Shikhar, I will have you banned.
Your racing career is over.
Forever.
It's over.
Shikhar, stop showing off.
Yeah. Deo Tibba, now.
- Where are we going?
- Deo Tibba.
It's where my bank
and my boyfriend are.
"It's a Harley"
Hey.
Do they know about your boyfriend
and your bank?
Sorry.
- Are you alright?
- Yes, I am alright.
Thank you God you saved us.
Hello. What are you doing?
Thank you so much.
Doing something bad to do some good.
Will you stay alive till my wedding?
Wedding?
Why?
You are getting married.
"I will kiss several frogs
before getting hitched."
That was your resolution.
Yeah. But the first frog
I kissed turned out to be my prince.
Tell me.
You are just repaying
the nappy changer's debt.
Aren't you?
Stop blabbering.
30th June. Block this date.
Be it heaven, hell or space.
Be there from wherever you are.
Bye.
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
Send your location to your boyfriend.
Oh god.
Come here.
Come on.
She ran away.
Laadli ran away.
Go on.
"Let's dance"
"The music's gonna
play non-stop today."
"...play non-stop..."
"Every corner will
be beautifully decked."
"Beautifully decked..."
"The music's gonna
play non-stop today."
"Every corner
will be beautifully decked."
"Looking attractive,
we won't stop partying tonight."
"Everyone will get high
and dance all night."
"But our sister,
who looks so cute."
"I wonder why she is so mute?"
"Doesn't say a word to anyone."
"Just repeats one thing..."
"I won't..."
"I won't go
to my beloved's house."
"Let's dance"
She ran away. Call Laadli back.
- Laadli ran away.
- Mom.
Mom.
Laadli ran away. Oh you are here?
I had a terrible nightmare.
I saw that you ran away.
"Shiny are the tresses
of my sister."
"Beautiful is the henna
on my sister's hands."
"Smear the turmeric on her."
"No more delays...hurry up."
"Bring her favourite dishes."
"Tell the DJ
to play her favourite song."
"Our sister, who is so sweet."
"Recently on Twitter,
she posted a tweet."
"Doesn't say a word to anyone."
"Just DM's one thing..."
"I won't..."
"I won't go to my beloved's house."
"On Twitter,
I've posted my wedding date."
"The guests have arrived,
but my brothers are late."
"I am eager to go
to my beloved's home,"
"just waiting for
your brother-in-law to show up."
"I will..."
"I will go to my beloved's home."
"Let's dance"
Laadli.
At the end of the aisle,
you will be Mrs.
Mrs. Laadli Katiyal of Mumbai.
Your husband is from Mumbai?
Don't say "husband".
Makes me feel weird.
Bro...you're a pro at helping brides elope.
I want to run away as well.
I don't want to get married.
Help.
My heart's pounding.
I had to kiss so many frogs.
I haven't even kissed this groom yet.
What will I do if I don't like him?
Relax.
Opium?
You want to take a stoned bride
to the altar.
Are you trying to make her life better
or worse?
Weird feeling?
Gone.
And?
Ready to get Mrs.
Ready to be your Mrs.
#Sanskrit Chant#
Brother.
Hail Cannabis.
"With you in my memories"
"I am waiting for you"
"You are my adornment, my love"
Don't leave me and go,
I want to live with you.
"We'll cry together,
laugh together."
"Show the world."
Can I order something--
Sorry, I have to take this.
I'll send you the mail.
- Yes.
- Milk?
Milk from me to you, I guess.
Imagine if the groom
was lactose intolerant?
He would be throwing up all night
in the bathroom.
I...am on an urgent
call with the US office.
It can take all night.
Since the time zones are different.
So...goodnight then?
Yeah, Mr. Smith.
Yeah, sorry.
The line got disconnected.
Yeah, we can do the paperwork.
"You've forgotten
the promises you made."
"You said you'll be back soon."
"We'll cry together,
laugh together."
"Show the world."
Mr. Shikhar Randhawa.
We regret to inform you,
that you've been banned
from participating,
in any professional
or amateur racing activities
for one year.
Your sponsorship from Speed Motors
stands cancelled.
Yeah, Bajju. Go ahead.
Your dad has been calling
you all morning.
Why don't you answer
your parent's calls?
Because I am not you!
Shikhar.
- Hello.
- Mr. Bajrang Das Khatri.
Sir...
sweets from our family wedding.
I am diabetic.
Sorry, sir.
One pin, please.
Very nice house.
Come, I'll show you my house.
This is my room.
This is where I sleep.
And this one?
It's locked.
The landlord's stuff.
I see.
May I?
Yes, of course.
Which side of the cupboard is mine?
As in?
Cupboard.
Do I take the right side or the left?
I've five suitcases filled with
my trousseau.
Alright.
All yours.
No, no...
Actually...
I don't want to displace you.
I turned the place upside down
as the one-day bride.
I feel guilty.
If you don't mind...
Can I make a quick trip to the office?
No, I don't mind.
Bye.
"My beloved."
Good morning.
Morning.
Unpacking, are you?
Can I help?
I am packing.
I'm flying to New York tonight.
Will leave straight from the office.
Only I had a valid visa, so...
How long is the trip?
One week.
I see.
- Laadli.
- Yes.
If you want to go home,
I can book your tickets for Shimla.
For a week?
No, I am fine.
Here's my credit card.
I've written down the pin.
And there's cash in this envelope.
I'll get you a card when I come back.
No. I can't.
Why?
I just can't.
It's okay.
We're married.
"My beloved"
"He is far away"
- Hello.
- Hello, Mr. Jeh Kotnis.
I am speaking from your
Bandhan Bank's card division...
Wrong number.
"My beloved"
No, wrong number.
I said wrong number!
"All eyes on me"
Hello.
Wrong number!
"He is far away"
Hello.
I said wrong number!
Wasn't this Jeh's phone number?
Don't know.
But now this is my phone number, okay.
Loan, bank, building service,
whoever you are.
Please stop calling, okay.
You guys have been calling me
for the last 200 kilometres
and driving me crazy.
Miss.
I am sorry.
"Lord."
Miss.
They recycle the number after 90 days.
They?
Telecomm company.
If the number isn't used for 90 days.
I Guess Jeh didn't use it.
So, it was allotted to me.
Thank you for telling me.
When someone's dead,
I won't keep calling
to hear his voice mail.
How long has it been?
It's been 182 days, 15 hours
and 47 minutes.
"Someone took my joys with him."
"And gave me sorrows in exchange."
- Shikhar? You?
- Yes me.
So suddenly?
I mean so suddenly...
without any intimation.
Is it some bad news?
Listen Mr. Bad News.
Put a brake on it.
I got a job in Mumbai.
- So here I am.
- But...
Cool chicks by the way.
Job? You mean the regular kind.
Yeah. So?
Ohh...
Even you had
to repay the nappy changer's debt?
Tragedy struck you too.
Hey...
I am not doing this job because of dad.
I got banned from racing.
So I thought I'd take up a job.
To pay the bills.
My friend owns a food delivery app.
He said come over.
The job's yours.
Ride your bike. Make a buck.
Have fun.
Where will you stay?
Here. Where else?
If you don't want me here,
then tell me now.
Was this the welcome hug
or the goodbye hug?
Of course, welcome.
You're here. Laadli's here.
Hail Babaji.
Now this city is going
to be fun.
Laadli.
What happened?
I don't know.
I told you to call her up.
Ask what happened.
I had to skip office!
- Laadli.
What happened?
Say something. What is wrong?
Tell us what happened?
If it's some sort of bad news
then tell him first.
Babaji!
Wedding gifts.
Freshly delivered by FedEx.
More than a hundred.
I jumped on the railway tracks,
upset my boss,
and skipped office without notice.
Because you sent me this text.
"Life and Death situation."
"For your sister's sake...
come soon."
Don't you have any shame?
What are you screaming for?
Let's just kill her.
- Can't you take a joke, Bajju?
- Hold her. My boss is calling.
Give me that, please.
I have a weapon. I have a weapon!
My boss has the power...to fire me!
Bajju, I'll shoot you in the eye.
- Don't come any closer.
- Enough talking. Catch her.
Hira Bai, open the door.
If I stay here it will be my last.
- Her husband isn't even at home.
- Bloody murderer!
We'll bury her somewhere under the bed.
Please...
When I am dead,
you'll be crying inconsolably.
No, we won't. We won't cry.
Sir, what kind of wife you have got.
Leave me.
I thought you'd be halfway to America.
The flight got rerouted from Delhi,
due to a rainstorm.
Leaves tomorrow.
Ohh...lovely.
Lunch?
Yeah. Let me.
Hira Bai.
I called them over
to open the wedding gifts.
Go ahead.
You'll get bored.
They won't stop bitching
while opening the gifts.
Go ahead.
Bishnoi Uncle and Family.
No need to open that.
It's a peacock.
Brass or stuffed.
You see... brother-in-law we told you.
"A peacock is dancing in my backyard."
Even when your great-great-grandchildren
get married,
even they will get a peacock.
General Ran--
Couldn't you pick something else?
General Randhawa.
Is he a relative of yours?
Divorced relative.
He and I got divorced.
He's my dad.
Or should I say ex-dad.
Shikhar, it's okay.
Have you heard of the cuddle bug?
That's Laadli.
This bug can cuddle attack
you anywhere, anytime.
Deadly.
And to make this deadly bug happy
is this gift.
Bajju. Gift from Kashyap.
- Kashyap.
- What? Gift from Kashyap?
One of you must have sent him a card.
I didn't invite him.
Who's Kashyap?
- Laadli's most tormented Romeo.
- What?
For two years,
he kept filling up my bike's tank...
Be quiet, what are you doing?
- Let him speak. He is right.
- Are you mad?
And also donated money
for Bajju's temple.
"Please bring Laadli to the window."
I wrote a song for her.
I want to sing it out for her.
What was it?
"Beloved, your dress is beautiful,
your veil's shiny."
"This is why I..."
Time out!
You two have overstayed.
Now leave.
Out!
They made a mess.
I'll clear it.
Make it clean like before.
Does he...know your taste?
Will you get it stitched?
I have a lot of dresses.
Maybe someday.
Hubby's gone to America.
Leaving me and my first credit card.
#nofilteronspends
Yeah!
Hello.
Keep your Tom and Jerry brothers away
from that card.
Otherwise, they will max it out.
So I can't enjoy the bonus of the wedding?
Why?
There is only one end to this attitude.
Your first fight with your husband.
Later, don't send me...
#swelled up eyes.
#nofilters
Okay.
Fill her up, mister.
"The tent is all set,"
"Flowers are decorated."
"Dessert is ready,"
"and the aroma's filling up
the air."
"A aedding house filled
with wedding guests."
"All my drunk friends say,"
"make me a drink or two."
"But you..."
"My love, don't stop me
today."
from drinking today."
"Dancing like a peacock."
I love Mumbai.
"Beautiful girls have made
my life miserable."
"Ask them for their location,"
"they say it's Chandigarh."
"Her mouth's watering
but she doesn't stop eating."
"In a fit of rage, she asks
who made it so spicy."
"If you want
I can get you some water."
"Pour you a glass myself."
"Or even get some sweets."
"I'll do whatever you say."
"You look so cute."
"My heart skips a beat."
"Why do you argue with me?"
"Why do you scream."
"Eat whatever you like..."
"All my drunk friends say,"
"make me a drink or two."
"My love, don't stop me today."
"Dancing like a peacock."
"Hey dear"
Hey Bajju. Don't open your front of mom.
we stayed out all night.
Yes Ladli, okay.
Hold on to her tight.
- I had too much fun.
-  "Dark nights"
"Filled with love"
"I'm waiting for you"
- Shikhu, enough.
- Hey, hold tight bro what happened?
Abhay. Abhay.
Hello.
Everything is fine here.
Shit.
Stay here, Bajju. Don't follow me.
I'll go alone.
Can we go home?
Did you see the credit card
notifications?
Are you mad?
Or just stupid?
Spend all you want.
Get high.
Dress like it's fancy dress
and go out looking like an idiot.
I don't care.
But bike?
If I ever see you on a bike again,
you can just pack
your stuff and leave.
You can yell at me all you want.
But don't tell me when I can
or cannot go to Shimla.
"Your tears make me cry."
'And this?'
'It's locked.'
'Landlord's stuff.'
Delivery for Ikroor Awasthi.
Counter number 9.
Bring the parcel up front.
If someone's dead,
I won't call to hear his voicemail.
How long has it been?
182 days, 15 hours...
47 minutes.
Thank you.
"O God"
Kind attention to passengers.
the local going from V.T
to thane is running 6 minutes late
- the inconvenience is regretted.
- Jeh, I miss you.
Happy birthday.
I swear I'm making a petition
to the railway board.
When someone's dead,
what's the point of playing his voice
over the PA system?
You can't get closure.
How will you forget Jeh?
It's not fair.
"O god"
Listen.
The counter is getting crowded.
Come soon.
"Since I got my hopes up,"
"can't stop crying."
"Don't let anyone
be so cruel, Lord."
Hello. Tough boy.
Hello. Can you hear me?
Tough boy.
"O god"
I am sorry.
I overdid it. Didn't I?
These bangles are very pokey.
It's only for a year.
Then I can take them off.
In Mumbai, no one takes notice.
You can take them off if you want,
you know.
Delivery for Ikroor Awasthi.
Counter number 9.
Bring the parcel up front.
Jeh, I miss you.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
- What happened?
- Shikhar Randhawa.
You cannot ride here.
You are not allowed.
But my name is on the list
of riders of enjoy.com
Yes, I know your name is there,
but still you can't ride.
What bull is this?
Call your manager.
You are banned for hooliganism.
Didn't you tell them that?
I did.
How was your journey
from Playboy to Pizza Boy?
And when my bride was lighting
your fireworks...
Faster, Shikhar. Faster.
Did you imagine
that would be your last best ride?
Did you?
Hey.
Sir...let's report him to the police.
He punched you.
I am the witness. This is wrong.
Leave it, Badri.
His racing days are over.
If we send him to jail,
his life will be over.
Breaking someone who is already
broken doesn't make anyone a hero.
Hello. Tough boy.
Hello. Can you hear me?
Don't let me see you here again.
Come, Badri.
You are done, pizza boy.
Hello.
Tough boy.
Can we meet?
I saw you.
At VT.
Counter number nine.
Delivery for Ikroor Awasthi.
Why didn't you say hi?
You were in a wheelchair.
I got scared.
But not anymore.
I can't stop thinking about you.
24/7 hours.
So can I see you?
Maybe.
In the next lifetime.
What?
Hello.
Hello!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sorry.
Pick up. Pick up.
Miss. Ikroor's friend.
- Please wait.
- Yes.
Listen, do you know where Ikroor is?
Get lost, you stalker.
Listen, I am not a stalker.
I have her number. I just spoke to her.
And I think she is going
to do something stupid.
Amazing.
Even stalkers have
become so creative these days.
Miss, please.
If I scream now,
the crowd will beat you up.
Understood. Out of my way.
It's been 182 hours,
15 hours and 47 minutes...
Since Jeh died.
She is planning on joining her.
Please tell me where she is.
Sixty-Nine Railway Colony, Chembur.
Open...
Hello.
"O god"
Wake up.
Ikroor!
"O god"
Tough boy.
For a year, I kept telling myself...
Live/Die...I don't care.
But when I was gasping for breath,
in that moment...
I felt the need to live.
I am glad you saved me.
Thank you.
Ikroor Awasthi.
Shikhar Randhawa.
Our fight isn't over yet, God.
Please put an end to it.
Please end it tomorrow.
Did You hear?
I was so happy when you called.
Asking me to go to dinner.
Our first fight ended today.
Thank God.
Hi, guys.
- Well.
- Oh, there you are.
She is Laadli.
My wife.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Sit.
So, how was your flight?
It was great.
She is cute, AK.
Among us boring corporate types,
like Christmas has arrived.
Sparkly.
She looks so nice.
Had I known it wasn't dinner for two,
but for many.
I wouldn't have shown
up looking like a Christmas tree.
So sparkly.
It was a compliment.
Today, we complete
one month of marriage.
Why didn't you remind me?
Would have made it dinner for two.
Anyway...
happy one-month anniversary.
Hello, Ikroor.
Hello.
No one took me to see him.
Will you?
Please?
Please.
Okay.
Shall I?
"It's love. It's love.
It's love. It's love. "
"You are the reflection of love."
"Love is the reflection of God."
"God is the reflection of water."
"Water is the reflection
of your soul."
"You must jump over high walls
and come for me."
"And bring every happiness
and joy along."
"Bring some embellishments
and some relationships."
"Together, we will cherish it."
"Bring some stories
and all your nights."
"We will spend them together."
"You must jump over high walls
and come for me."
"It's my love...
my love...my love."
"They say God fulfils every wish,"
"He will fulfil yours someday."
"The relationship...
between two hearts,"
"is the reflection of God."
"Together, we will cherish
this relationship."
"You must leave the world behind
and come to me."
"Come dressed
in the colour of love."
"And with adorned hands."
"Together, we'll cherish it."
"Bring some embellishment
and some relationships."
"Together, we will cherish it."
𝙁𝙤𝙧 𝙢𝙤𝙧𝙚 𝙨𝙪𝙗𝙩𝙞𝙩𝙡𝙚𝙨 𝙫𝙞𝙨𝙞𝙩 𝙎𝙪𝙗𝙩𝙞𝙩𝙡𝙚𝙕.𝙘𝙤𝙢
"You must jump over high walls
and come for me."
Sparkly suits you.
- Hey, hi.
- Shikhu.
Laadli, please.
It's Bajju's treat.
Is it?
He definitely got a raise.
Otherwise, we would be eating
vadapav outside Mahalaxmi station.
Put a zip on it on your 'ouch' comments.
I did get a raise.
And my first foreign trip.
Great.
I will remove the evil eye.
Let me ward off the evil eye.
Protect from demons,
poisonous animals,
and evil sights that mean harm.
Spit on it.
Do you know how stupid you are?
- Spit on it.
- Yeah, burger's mine.
Soon you'll have one more
to ward off the evil eye.
Extra?
- Girlfriend?
- Yes.
But wasn't I supposed
to find one for you?
But I found the perfect one, Laado.
The one the astrologer suggested?
Not Baba Mubarak's
b*****t prediction again.
Shikhar.
Remember the day
when it was raining heavily.
The entire city was flooded.
No power. No network.
I heard a scream that was very loud.
That's where I saw her.
Same to same.
Babaji's prediction.
My future wife.
Dressed in a lotus pink sari.
Softer than a lotus.
Ditto as Babaji said.
Sitting on top of sparkling
water with legs crossed.
- A white bird will be sitting on her right.
- Bajju.
And she was calling out for heaven.
Siri. Siri. Can you call the BMC, please?
Siri. Siri. Siri. Siri.
She was calling Siri on her phone.
Not heaven.
What bull.
S for "Swarg" (heaven).
S for Siri.
Don't take everything literally
if you don't know.
Listen...did you say hi or hello?
I fixed her meter box.
Then I took her in my arms.
Took her to dry ground.
Put her in a taxi.
Dropped her at a hotel
and came back home.
Bajju the saviour.
Glory to Babaji.
You will praise Babaji more
when you meet her.
She is so wow.
I'll be right back.
Hello.
- Yeah.
- How's your job going on?
Going good.
Shauna, they are...
Laadli and Shikhar. I know.
Bajju told me so much about you guys,
there is no need for introductions.
We all knew Bajju will have
a wife one day.
But Bajju's girlfriend would be
so gorgeous.
This is a shock to all of us.
And anyway, the journey from girlfriend
to wife is just a signature away.
Shikhu... keep quiet.
- What are you doing?
- Keep quiet.
Bajju.
Yes?
Is that a proposal?
Will you marry me?
"With you"
And that's how...
I said yes.
Why do I have a flight today...
don't feel like going.
Giggles... Then don't go please.
So cute.
Its a traffic jam.
Not going to clear soon.
I've an evening shift.
I am walking.
Come on, let's walk.
Would have been more fun
if Shauna was with us?
Now you must get us,
family discounts on flight tickets.
- Yes, definitely.
- Won't you, Bajju.
Yes, Laadli.
Hey, Shikhar. Why are you so quiet?
Tell me what you think about her?
What is the hurry to get married?
So you don't like her.
She said "yes" on Insta.
Didn't that seem weird?
You ran off with the money I kept
for my family temple.
Didn't that seem weird?
But we still kiss him.
Share our home.
Weird, right?
You don't have to share your house.
And you...go kiss your hubby.
Leave me alone.
What did I do?
Why are you screaming at me?
I am just a silent spectator.
He is the one screaming at you.
And he is doing it because he thinks,
as always, you'll diffuse
the situation as mother India.
Otherwise, our relationship will go
to the garbage.
By the way, these are not my words.
These are his mother's words.
This is what she said
when she left his father.
I am dumping this relationship
in the garbage.
You are allergic
to others' happiness.
Mr. Colonel Rotton Mouth Randhawa.
Shikhar, what are you doing?
Stop it.
Where are you going, Shikhar?
Shikhar, if you leave,
we will be history.
Is that what you want?
What do you think about her?
I found her sweet.
Frankly.
Shikhar. Where are you going?
Please, Shikhar. Don't go.
Please. Please.
Go and apologise.
Say sorry to Shikhar.
You insulted his dad first.
He insulted my life.
"You are my friend"
Yes... Yes...
Okay.
Okay, okay...
All the chairs are empty,
and still, you choose
to sit next to the boss.
Brave man you are
Mr. Bajrang Das Khatri.
Very brave.
I was in the mood to get
some firing today, that's why.
Homesick?
Any family friends in Mumbai?
Brother and sister, sir.
Cousins.
But just like real ones.
That's my younger brother.
Jaishankar Krupal.
Recently he became
MD of Speed Motors.
My little brother.
I am proud of him.
Proud of him.
Sir...your little brother is
MD of Speed Motors.
Why would I discount
my vice president's professional opinion,
and help Shikhar Randhawa?
Because, in this case,
the ban was personal, sir,
and not professional.
I am sorry, young man,
but you'll have to come up
with a reason better than that.
Sir, ask me a better question,
and I'll give you a better reason.
Are you a vegetarian?
Yes, sir.
Why don't you eat meat?
According to me,
it's not good manners.
That's why I don't eat it.
Good manners?
Yes, sir.
We take more from nature
than we need.
Milk, fruits, honey.
Isn't that bad enough?
Now, if we insist on chopping
someone's leg
and marinating it in spices.
Isn't that too much, sir?
It's not good manners, sir.
That's why I don't eat it.
I mean if you are jealous of someone,
then you can insult him.
Cancel his sponsorship.
That should be enough, sir.
But banning someone for a lifetime.
Cut off his lifeline.
Not good manners, sir.
It's not good manners.
Bajju. Your airport cab is here.
Come on.
Do you want to miss your flight?
My first foreign trip.
bye, happy journey...
he did not come to wish me...
And another thing, Laadli.
I think it's my fault.
Because I said several things
about his dad in a fit of rage.
I shouldn't have said it.
I found love.
But lost my brother.
I grew older,
but not smarter.
Thank you, God.
Here's your new return ticket.
It's a little expensive.
But she will be on this flight.
Do you know who?
Your girlfriend, Shauna.
This is her route.
She will bring you tea and coffee.
For 18 hours. Have fun.
Cutie.
Why are you leaving me alone with
this cuddle bug?
Now my foreign trip is going to be fun.
Wish me a happy journey.
Happy journey.
Bye, Bajju. Take care.
Stop, mister.
Why is he coming back?
Did he forget something?
What happened?
Your ban's been cancelled.
What?
Now, you can race anywhere in India.
No one's going to stop you.
See you. Or I'll be late.
Enjoy your meal, sir.
Thank you.
Sir your blanket
Excuse me, ma'am.
Where can I find Ms. Shauna?
She is in the upper deck pantry.
Thank you.
Welcome.
"Why unknowingly..."
"my eyes have turned moist."
"I still have a smile on my face."
"But several questions on my mind."
"The nights that you spent
away from me..."
"I'm aware of it."
"O unfaithful one,
I've heard."
"You are happily living
with someone else."
"Happily living with someone else."
"Tell me how you did it?"
"How could you be so unfaithful?"
"I need to know."
"How long do
I keep waiting for you."
"Where do I go."
"Can I tell God to make you mine?
- Happy Valentine's Day.
-  "O unfaithful one, I've heard."
- Look to your right.
-  "...celebrating my ruination."
"...celebrating my ruination."
"O unfaithful one, I've heard."
"You burn my pictures
when you are alone."
"Burn my pictures
Happy birthday.
Bajju...
He's a fraud.
That Babaji is a...
0fraud.
What..
- Bajju.
- Brother-in-law... gift...
I...
- Abhay...
- He's out.
- Fraud. Babajje is a fraud.
- Bajju.
Fraud. Fraud.
Bajju.
- Babajje is a fraud.
- Bajju. The astrologer.
Fraud.
Fraud... fraud?
Bajju...
Brother-in-law left for the office.
I should too.
Your clothes are dirty, Bajju.
I'll get you Abhay's clothes.
Wear those.
Bajju. You were leaving
without saying bye.
There is some cake in here.
Eat it at lunchtime.
And here's more so you can share.
And your phone.
You were leaving it behind.
Listen...should I come along?
We can return together
in the evening local.
It's okay.
I think this belongs to brother-in-law.
"O unfaithful one, I've heard."
"You are waiting for me to die."
"...waiting for me to die."
"O unfaithful one, I've heard."
"You're giving
my share of love to him."
"Giving my share of love to him."
"Being yours..."
"I lost everything I had."
"I spent my nights staying awake,"
"couldn't sleep a single day."
You crossed all limits
You denied everything
I wanted to tell you something
but you still denied it
"What you think are the rains,"
"are my tears."
"With your love...where do I go?"
"I'm lost...and so is my love."
Hello.
Did you know about the affair?
He told me before the wedding.
But I thought they broke up.
"I slept with my sorrows"
"Next to me"
"You think its raining,"
"but these are my tears."
Why did you put up with
this useless marriage for so long?
For mom and myself.
What the f*** man, Laadli!
For years, mom did everything
she could in her power.
Just to see my married.
Isn't it my duty
to try and make
my husband smile like this for me?
Laadli man...
I'll go get him right now.
He's in the office, isn't he?
I'll go get him.
Then why did you call me?
If you wanted to do nothing,
then why did you call me?
It's my nature.
If I want to cry, call Shikhar.
But not this time.
This time I must act on my own.
It's called growing up. Right?
Laadli.
I borrowed your suit for Bajju.
It had the key to that room.
I cannot stay here anymore.
I am leaving.
"Kohl, embellishments,
these joys are fake."
"They look upset
when you are not here."
Where are you going?
Shimla.
Fine. I'll drop you.
I am not the one who needs pickup
and drop in this house.
"Kohl, embellishments,
these joys are fake."
"They look upset
when you are not here."
The moon is where it was
only the stars with it broke
without the stars
the words you will tell to whom...
my love
Laado
Isn't this what you wanted, child?
Divorce.
I got the papers ready.
I even spoke to Abhay's mom.
At first, she refused.
But I said,
"No. This is completely my fault".
I showed these happy dreams
of marriage to my Laado.
Otherwise,
my Laado was happy as the beauty queen.
I am to be blamed for it.
Please grant us the divorce.
-  "I pity my eyelids"
- Please grant us the divorce.
-  "Moist for so long"
- Im so sorry beta...Im so sorry.
"Haven't had a wink"
Not even one teardrop shone
I swear these eyes did not cry
You tell me
How will I sleep in this condition...
my love
Laadi's marriage fell apart.
My life was shattered.
Shikhar is broken,
because we were broken.
This city didn't suit us.
Not one bit.
Yes yes yes yes yes.
Come on, come on come on.
Yes.
I lost because all
my focus was on Laadli.
Champion means
no excuses tough boy.
Thank God you don't ride a bike.
Otherwise, my rep would be...
I am sorry.
Ikroor, I am sorry.
Sorry, I forgot.
Really sorry.
Hug please.
Lately, my mood's been so off,
I say stupid things.
Sorry. Sorry.
Is...that Abhay?
I hate his face.
He is a biker.
And you didn't investigate
his background.
Before Laadli's wedding.
- Him?
- He is no biker.
But...his photo is
in your biking club.
This here used to be a wall of fame
your talking about this guy right?
Best bloody biker, you know.
Abhay Singh Katyal.
He was a champion rider.
Was Amazing racer.
Superb.
What a love story he had.
Unforgettable.
Legend.
He was a legend.
Yeah, Shikhar.
Laadli.
That girl with Abhay.
I found out more
about that girl and Abhay.
"And I love you so..."
Rajlaxmi Cariapa.
Tell that idiot of yours,
hands off my gate.
Father.
What's the point of telling him now?
I think he
and all the neighbours heard it.
Hold it.
They heard.
But didn't understand.
Stupid biker boy
See...he understood.
I've to go now, bye. Please.
Do what you want.
You are going to marry that boy
who owns the coffee plantation.
It's decided.
Let's go.
How was your race today.
Who is this coffee plantation boy?
Jealous?
"Come to me."
"Come to me, my love."
"Don't be upset with me, beloved."
"For my sake."
"Makes my heart skip a beat..."
"This separation."
"You said we'll be together...
forever."
"My eyes are...
welled up with tears."
"Tell me..."
"Tell me...
will you keep your promise or not?"
"I am right beside you."
"Why are we..."
"Why are we still apart?"
Where were you all morning?
I texted you we are going
to Lonavala.
For a race in the morning.
Happy Dussera mom-dad.
Wait, Rajji.
Let's decide once and for all.
Either you leave that useless biker boy,
or this house!
Don't look at mom.
I am telling you.
Just get out of my house I say.
Go live with that biker boy of yours.
But I don't want this everyday nonsense.
- Dad.
- Just get out I say. Out!
- Say sorry.
- Say sorry to dad.
Why should I say sorry?
Every day he tells me to get out.
Get lost.
Go with that Biker boy...etcetera.
- He will forget everything by tomorrow.
- No, mom.
And I won't marry
that coffee plantation boy.
He told me to get out.
I am leaving.
Rajjee... stop.
"I've heard many have pined."
"But no one has pined like me."
Stop her she's leaving.
"After walking for miles I realised..."
"There is no place like home."
"Every time..."
"Every time my arms look for you."
"I am walking down your lane."
"Take me in your arms."
"Why are we still apart?"
"Where our destination lies..."
"No one is aware."
- "Where are we headed."
- No, let's go.
"Who is aware"
"Take me with you"
"Heart is..."
Look, what happened?
Let's run.
The biker...
"O bird..."
"Little bird..."
"Fly back to my courtyard."
What are you doing here
you bloody murderer?
- Stop.
- Wait a minute.
You killed my daughter bloody nonsense.
You killed my daughter bloody.
You fooled around with her
all this while.
Now what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
You killed her.
Get out of here.
You were playing with my daughter.
Get out.
Since that day Abhay
was never seen again...
On the racing circuit.
He left everyone.
His house, friends, dreams, family.
He changed completely.
What to do now?
Laadli?
Are you not at home?
I am at home.
It's me.
Open the door.
Abhay.
Is my stuff still in my room?
Or did you move them?
They are still there.
Laadli.
Can't we delay this divorce decision?
I mean for a couple of months.
I am staying, Abhay.
But we'll live like flatmates.
No questions, no explanations.
No hope for each other.
Okay?
"Kohl, embellishments,
these joys are fake."
"They look upset
when you are not here."
"The further you go,"
"How can you rest, my love."
Sorry.
Actually, I think I dropped hook
of my hearing somewhere.
I've to attend a friend's wedding.
The cab is waiting for me downstairs.
So I'll see you.
Can I drop you.
Don't you have an office to go to?
Today is Saturday.
But you have office every Saturday.
Not this Saturday.
Call me when the party is over.
I will come pick you up. Okay.
Would you like to join me?
In a love marriage,
love is like thunder.
That takes us by surprise.
And...enslaves us forever.
But when marriages are arranged,
what is their definition of love?
I feel...
it's a message to fall in love.
From the mind to the heart.
Go fall in love.
You have the permission.
So this is a love marriage as well.
The only difference is...
Our near and dear ones are involved
in this permission.
Permission to say I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
"Beloved your..."
Come on. Let's dance.
No, darling.
You dance with your hubby.
I am staying put.
Laadli's dear Hubby.
Do you know what we decided
when we were in ICU together?
If I survive and get married,
then we'll dance together.
I wasn't in the country for her wedding.
But I am taking her with me now.
Come on.
- Come on, Laadli.
- Stop it.
"Beloved, your dress is lovely,
the veil's shiny."
"That's why I try to impress you."
"Beloved, your dress is lovely,
the veil's shiny."
"That's why I try to impress you."
"I didn't know you were so unique."
"All the other girls drink vodka,
you drink wine."
"The way you skirt your eyes,
is unique."
"The way you skirt eyes
and lock again has floored me."
"Beloved, your dress is lovely,
the veil's shiny."
"That's why I try to impress you."
Kashyap.
- Hi.
- Laadli.
You became a singer.
How cool.
Thanks to all the practice
I did under your window.
Nonsense.
How long are you in Mumbai?
This is where I live now.
My husband works here.
Guys.
The party is shifting to the pub.
Please don't stop dancing.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
If I borrow you for a dance,
will your husband doubt you?
No, of course not.
"I am always finding you"
"I have no other wish"
"Forget the world, it is corrupt"
"Love was a passion for the likes
of Ranjha and Heer."
"Now it's become
an addiction for the rich."
"Guys get cool haircuts
to impress you."
"You make my heart skip a beat."
The brightest chandelier in the world
has arrived in your house.
Congratulations, Laadli's hubby.
Congratulations.
The bride thanked you
after her speech.
Why?
I wrote her speech.
That's why.
I have a wedding vows business.
I write speeches for all brides.
All word of mouth.
Nothing much.
It was good.
You were all fired up
when someone called you a Chritmas tree.
Remember.
When he called you a chandelier,
I thought you'd ask me
to beat him up.
No one takes Kashyap's
nonsense seriously.
He's been crazy
about me since kindergarten.
No. He still is.
Yeah, so?
Why are you so upset?
It's not like you are crazy about me?
If someone else is crazy about it,
then that's good.
Shines my self-respect.
Laadli.
I think...I'll go to the office.
But you said you have a holiday.
I do.
But doesn't mean I can't go.
"When you are away."
"My heart aloof."
Which platform
is your sister coming on?
Platform number 2.
She will be here any minute.
- Hi.
Sirat. my sister.
Your sister is a loco pilot.
Wow.
True or false? Isn't this
the best lunch date of your life?
True.
Behind VT station,
isn't this restaurant
Mumbai's best kept secret?
True.
My sister is the best in the world?
Second best.
Do you have a sister?
Cousin.
I don't have
any real brother and sister.
Oh...my online class will start soon.
It's compulsory.
So I'll go give
my attendance at that table.
- I'll just come.
- No problem.
Didn't Ikroor tell you.
She got a scholarship in America.
University with Ivy League.
Full scholarship
in computer graphics, you know.
She can become
the best gaming programmer.
Not here, but out there.
For her wheelchair is just an accessory,
not a handicap.
I see.
Do you?
You are feeling very macho, don't you?
As Roo's rescue operation.
Roo doesn't need your rescue.
Do you know why she is working
behind the ticket counter?
To add working hours.
On her resume.
That's all.
She is brilliant.
Brilliant.
And she deserves a brilliant life.
Not some wannabe rider like you,
who can give her a shit life? Right.
You are shit.
And you'll be a shit all your life.
You don't have money
or any hopes of making money.
Nor any family
to see you through tough times.
I will slap you.
In short, you are a bad proposition
for Roo from every angle.
Hello.
Did I miss something?
Just you darling.
Let's go.
Are you going to America?
The decision is still pending.
Because I will have to leave nice people.
So still pending.
"Lord."
- Sister has invited you over for tea.
- Excuse me.
Are you scared
she is expecting the wedding cavalry?
Pick up the phone, Shikhar.
Shikhar.
Ikroor.
The race is very close.
I won't get any time
between doing laps and my job.
So we can't meet for a few days.
Sirat told you to stay away from me, right?
Shikhar.
Won't you even fight...
for our sake?
Shikhar.
You will be ok no?
Promise.
If you breaking up with me,
and want to know whether I will try
to kill myself?
No, Shikhar.
I won't.
I am no longer that weak, stupid girl.
Thanks to you.
Be happy, okay.
"If you learn to live without me,
I won't worry about you either."
You Sure ...this is the house.
Should I come along?
I can be your silent moral support.
Remember.
as a family we can only be two down.
Not three down.
- Yes.
- Hello, uncle.
I am Laadli Chibbar.
So?
Rajlaxmi's friend. From Shimla.
I was in Mumbai
and thought I should meet you.
My wife can't bear...
talking about rajjee
talking about Rajlaxmi, so.
So I think it's good
you should leave, please.
- Sir.
- Thank you.
Shashitharan Cariappa.
what is this nonsense?
Child. Come inside.
Okay.
Talk about my Raji.
Talk, please.
My husband will cry,
but you don't mind.
You don't cry.
Rainbows don't cry.
Daughters don't cry.
Is Laadli at home?
No. She's gone out.
Her last client dealt in cash.
I just picked this up for her.
Give it to her when she comes back.
If she comes give it to her.
Can I come inside?
Did Laadli tell you that I race?
I saw your photo
in the racing club's corridor.
People still talk about you.
Abhay Singh Katyal.
You are like a legend.
Your rides,
trophies friends, biker code.
Rajlaxmi.
Does Laadli know?
I've a race on the 27th.
Do come if you can.
"I loved you more than God."
"Still I couldn't make you mine."
""Always dwelled in your heart..."."
"but couldn't
reach your heartbeats."
It's not a favour
if someone supports you.
Do not mention me
if someone asks about your woes.
Second best strawberries of the season.
For my rainbow.
Uncle.
"Beloved...love is true."
"Destiny's craves
for something else."
"Beloved...love is true."
Happy 28th birthday, Rajlaxmi.
Thank you so much Laadli.
It's a beautiful cake.
Thank you.
We are celebrating because...
Raji was in our life.
but now she isn't.
It's okay, God's wish.
I will wait until we'll meet again
and we are together,
and you'll hug me and say "I love you".
"Never imagined"
I love you.
"If you will fly"
I am sorry I am crying, but...
"Who will grace our home"
I just miss her so much you know.
Sorry.
Today I too want to make
a confession to Rajee.
I'm not ladli chibber.
I'm ladli singh katyal.
Abhay's wife.
You mean that scoundrel. That rogue.
He's a fraud. He's a cheat!
Raj is dead because of him.
And he carried on with his life.
Bloody nonsense.
I can kill him, you know that.
Raji.
Raji is so special,
I saw it through Abhay's eyes.
This is Abhay's house.
There is a room for Raji.
No one's allowed in that room.
Not even me.
Laadli.
The chairs are empty.
You can call someone
from your family if you want.
Hello Abhay.
"I am worried so much for you..."
"I've forgotten about myself."
"For you, I've renounced the world
and wandered around."
"Come back to me...
before I become infamous."
"Every breath I take is for you."
"I know what's in my heart,
only God knows what's in your heart."
"Every breath..."
"Every breath I take is for you."
Raji said...mom and dad cannot live
without me for more than three months.
Only two days were left
for three months to be completed.
Two days later I will leave.
And two days later she was gone.
She was gone.
Meeting Raji's favourite person,
we are really delighted.
"Whoever looks at me...says..."
"I am crazy about my beloved."
"All I have is your name,"
"that's all I have."
"I've dedicated all my life
to my beloved."
"Every breath..."
"Every breath I take is for you."
"I've one heart, one life."
"Both are for you."
"Sit before me..."
"Let me ward off the evil eye
before I touch you."
"I've written few words
which I must convey."
"A story where you are
the queen and me the king."
"Come back to me..."
"I've been pining for you."
"Every breath I take is for you."
You rode your bike to meet your mom.
Why?
It's her happy birthday.
She was sleeping around with that man.
We saw her when we came back.
And you still went to meet her?
Tell me.
I love my mom.
You can't be my son.
You are shit.
And you will be shit all your life.
Wannabe rider like you.
- You are shit.
- Who can give her a shit life!
And you will be shit all your life.
I am not shit.
She deserves a good life.
- I am not shit.
- Shut up.
- I love my mom.
I am not shit.
- She was sleeping around with that man.
- I am not.
Shikhar, help me.
Of course.
What happened?
I am standing at the bus stop
and she is walking towards me.
Who?
Shauna.
My heartbeat is racing at
2000 beats per second.
Turn around with swag and say
"Hey what's up".
Bajju.
That's all, okay.
Tone casual.
Like she doesn't matter.
You have moved on, okay.
Hi.
How are you?
Copy me.
Hey, what's up?
Finish your call, I will wait.
Tell her. This call will take time.
She isn't someone who would wait.
Say it, Bajju.
I wanted to talk to you.
Bajju, tell me.
I don't want to talk to you ever again.
Are you nuts...
not just a heartbreak but leftover bloody
bleeding heart ripped and showed to her
Not today,
not tomorrow, not the day after.
Never.
i felt like I was the only one lacking
that's why I couldn't get your love
There is some moisture in my eyes only
that's why I couldn't see your love properly
I was crying inconsolably on the bus.
I am in the taxi.
But seeing her crying,
I wanted to go to her and say...
I know what you wanted to say.
Sorry, I left you.
My swag is nothing.
I can't stop loving you.
Shikhar, did you break up too?
Shikhar, delivery for Shikhar Randhawa.
Brother. Your parcel.
Take this sir.
I am flying out tomorrow night.
To America.
Or I would have
to attend the race tomorrow.
To cheer for you.
Definitely.
Listen, tough boy.
I just want to tell you...
you are magic on that bike.
So just go and win that race.
All the best.
Protect from demons,
poisonous animals,
and evil sights that mean harm.
Spit on it.
Do it, Shekhar.
This will clear your mind
of the negativity General Randhawa.
Do it.
You have to win, Shekhar.
- Come on.
- Spit on it.
Spit on it.
Aren't they your rivals?
Why is Abhay talking to them?
I don't like it.
Like I said...
Your husband has
a legend status on this circuit.
- I think you should readdress this question.
- Fine.
All the best.
Just believe in yourself.
You can win
Pizza boy.
Spoke to my runaway bride.
She had a break-up again.
She is broken.
And broken-hearted.
She wants to come back.
But how is it going to be?
Messed up life.
Hers and mine.
And you are to be blamed for it.
Bijoy. You have to win. Finish him.
Break him.Okay.
Gosh, I am so nervous.
I am feeling nervous.
You'll have a new name.
You're a s***e, Randhawa.
- I'll break you today.
- You are shit.
And you'll be shit all your life.
Why are they blocking him?
Yeah, look.
Doesn't matter how many races you win.
You are shit in my eyes..
always you'll be shit.
You are shit.
My beloved...
You are an apple of my eyes
"Set me free"
Take me there, please.
We've to get on the racetrack.
Yes, right now damnit.
'Tough boy. You are magic on that bike.'
'Won't you fight for me?'
My beloved...
Look up Ladli
No.
look up...
You are an apple of my eyes
It's a Harley.
My hero brother.
That's one core team.
It's a Harley.
Hooray.
And the new champion
is Shikhar Randhawa.
You will call Shikhar.
And say
"He's a Speed Motor boy now".
We are ready to sponsor him. Got it?
You won.
Yeah.
We won.
Cuddle bug I have to go.
I will have to fight for her sake.
For Ikroor.
I will take you to her.
We've to get there in 30 minutes,
otherwise--
Abhay, this is life
and death for Shikhar.
Isn't it better if he drives?
- 20 minutes.
- Let's go.
Shikhar, I'll deal with her tough
loco-pilot sister.
You...focus on Roo.
Roo...I won.
The championship is mine.
I even got the sponsorship.
I have money now.
I'll come to the US to say sorry.
For not picking up the phone.
For hurting you.
I was an idiot.
I had a late realisation
that I deserve you.
Okay, bye.
Wait, Roo.
That's all I needed to hear.
"Lord"
Excuse me.
You are Ikroor's sister, right?
I am Abhay.
And this is my wife Laadli.
- Hi.
- Shikhar's sister.
And that's Bajju. His brother.
The kind that stays
through good times and bad.
That's right.
He has his family for good
and bad times.
Ikroor deserves the best.
I agree.
And we...are the best.
"Lord"
When life blesses you with abundance,
you can't complain.
Not even with the 7:30 local.
Because that's where I found
my better half.
"Don't stare with your wicked eyes"
"I'll fall in love."
Shikhar. I am nervous.
Don't. Shikhar, don't be crazy.
"I'll lose my heart."
"This is our story,"
Bajju, what are you doing?
"An entire lifetime..."
Ready to be mister!
"Got a question for you,
what is your opinion."
"We can be together
if you listen to me."
"The water's shiny,
shiny, shiny."
"And the day's sunny,
sunny, sunny."
"The water's shiny,
shiny, shiny."
"And the day's sunny,
sunny, sunny."
" My eyes are always searching for you."
"The heart has fallen for the sweet words"
"I'll walk along with you."
"I'm always searching for you"
"The youth is crazy."
"Let me tease you"
" Got a question for you,
what is your opinion..."
" We can be together
if you listen to me."
" The water's shiny,
shiny, shiny."</."
"The water's shiny,
shiny, shiny."
"And the day's sunny,
sunny, sunny."
"The water's shiny,
shiny, shiny."
"And the day's sunny,
sunny, sunny."